NOR AZRIN BINTI MOHAMAD



Address : Lot 1557 Kg. Kelar Tok Pukang, 17040

Pasir Mas, Kelantan.

Telephone Number : 013-4473324

E-mail : norinmohamad@gmail.com

PERSONAL PARTICULAR

Age : 23 years old Marital Status : Single

Gender: Female **Date of Birth**: 05th March 1993

Race : Malay

Nationality : Malaysian

PROFESSIONAL OBJECTIVE

To be a highly-skilled medical team of pathologists, science officer, medical laboratory technologists, technician and specialists work together to determine the presence, extent or absence of disease and provide valuable data needed to evaluate the effectiveness of treatment.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Institution : Institute of Medical Science Technology (UniKL MESTECH)

Level Bachelor in Clinical Laboratory Science (Hons.)

C.G.P.A : 2.63

Institution : Matriculation College of Perlis

Level : Science

C.G.P.A : 2.51

School : MARA Junior Science College Pengkalan Chepa, Kelantan

SPM : 5A's, 1B, 3C's

School : MARA Junior Science College Pasir Tumboh, Kelantan

PMR : 8A's

		O-CURRICULUM ACHIEVEMENT			
Place	Year	Details			
Makmal Kesihatan Awam Kota Bharu (MKA KB)	2016	 Participate in Course of Slide Preparation and Diagnose of Microfilaria, Parasite Unit Committee member in Course of Parasite Malaria, Parasite Unit Committee member in Course of TIBI, TIBI Unit 			
Institute of Medical Science Technology (UniKL MESTECH)	2016- 2012	Involve in GPMS Facilitator Trainee UniKL Mestech – UniKL MIAT Committee member of Maal Hijrah Celebration 1435H Participate in Student Entrepreneurship Association Participate in Fight Back Clinique UniKL MESTECH – UniKL MFI First Prize Award of Volleyball Female Team in USSC			
Matriculation College of Perlis	2012- 2011	 Participate in English Short Story of Creative Writing Competition First Prize Award of Volleyball Female Team in MSSC 			
		WORKING EXPERIENCE			
Industrial training		Career			
MKA KB (Medical Laboratory Technologist) (25 th Jan – 12 th May 2016)		 Assistant Store Manager at 7-Eleven 2017) Promoter at Arrymitz Enterprise (Sept 2016) Reading Teacher at Genius Aulad 2016-Sept 2016) Shaklee Independent Distributor (2015-2017) Promoter at Peace Collection (2013) Promoter/Worker at MK Furniture (2011) 			
		LABORATORY SKILLS			
Microbiology		 Streaking, Staining, Culture & Sensitivity Test Identification of bacteria Microparticle Agglutination Test (Lepto) 			
Immunology		Particle-Agglutination Test			
Biochemistry		 Urine Identification Test Samples and Electrolyte analysis			
Hematology		Phlebotomy and Blood test			
Histology		Preparing tissue samples			
Serology		Lepto and Rotavirus Rapid Test			
TIBI		 Ogawa and Lowenstein-Jensen media preparation Smear, Culture, Drug Susceptibility Testing and 			

Parasite

• Identification of Blood film Malaria Parasite

LANGUAGES SKILL							
Languages	Writing	Speaking					
Malay	Excellence	Excellence					
English	Moderate	Moderate					
Mandarin	Weak	Weak					
COMPUTER SKILLS							
Microsoft Office Application (Wo	Advanced						
Windows Movie Maker	Moderate						
Adobe Photoshop	Moderate						
SPSS	Moderate						

STRENGTHS / PERSONAL QUALITIES

I have the ability to think things through in a logical and systematic manner; willing to learn something new

Easy-going person; hard-working and independent; enjoy creating order and structure; straight-forward and honest

Will follow projects and works through to completion; driven to fulfill my duties as good as possible; highly participated and co-operative team-player

Goal-oriented and full of self-motivated; and will use logical analysis to understand and decide something.

REFERENCES

Shabihah Binti Lazin

Company Supervisor, Makmal Kesihatan Awam Kota Bharu

Tel: 09-7138000

Ilyas Syafiq Bin Darul Ridzuan

Industrial Training Coordinator, UniKL MESTECH

Tel: 03-87395894 (ext. 294)